Booth Tarkington Papers, 1812-1956 (bulk 1899-1946): Finding Aid C0062
Manuscripts Division
- Series 7: Printed Material/Magazines, 1899 May-1946; 31 boxes
  - Subseries 7A: Magazines, A - Z, 1899 May-1946; 26 boxes
    - Cosmopolitan, 1917 November-1931 October; 1 box (Box 225)
    - Cosmopolitan - Em, 1936 August-1946 December; 1 box (Box 226)
    - Et - Forum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 227)
    - Forward - Good Housekeeping, 1912 September-1944 May; 1 box (Box 228)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1945 October-November; 1 box (Box 229)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1901 January-1922 August; 1 box (Box 229)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1912 September-1922 June; 1 box (Box 230)
    - H - L, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 231)
    - Ma - McClure's Magazine, 1899 May-1897 September; 1 box (Box 232)
    - McClure's Magazine, 1899 October-1926 June; 1 box (Box 233)
    - Me - Na, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 234)
    - Ne - O, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 235)
    - Ra - The Red Book Magazine, 1921 May-1922 October; 1 box (Box 236)
    - The Red Book Magazine - Sa, 1923 May-1944 October; 1 box (Box 237)
    - Sc - T, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 238)
    - W - Y, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 239)
    - American Magazine, 1917 January-1945 February; 1 box (Box 240)
    - Collier's, 1932 May-June; 1 box (Box 241)
    - Harper's Weekly, 1910 April; 1 box (Box 241)
    - Ladies Home Journal, 1922 November-1927 December; 1 box (Box 241)
    - Ladies Home Journal, 1928 January-1945 April; 1 box (Box 242)
    - McCall's, 1922 August-1938 August; 1 box (Box 243)
    - McClure's, 1917 October-1920 July; 1 box (Box 243)
    - Metropolitan, 1914 April-1920 April; 1 box (Box 244)
    - Pictorial Review, 1919 June-1925 December; 1 box (Box 244)
    - The Ladies Home Journal, 1917 October-1925 December; 1 box (Box 245)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1907 August 24-1929 April 13; 1 box (Box 245)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1930 May 31-1936 December 19; 1 box (Box 246)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1937 February 6-1945 May 19; 1 box (Box 247)
    - Woman's Home Companion, 1928 January-1935 April; 1 box (Box 247)
  - Subseries 7B: Ephemera, dates not examined; 4 boxes
    Consists of various ephemera collected by Booth Tarkington.
    - Ephemera, dates not examined; 4 boxes (Box 248, Box 249, Box 250, Box 251)
  - Subseries 7C: Clippings, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of various clippings collected by Booth Tarkington.
    - Clippings, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 252)
- Series 8: Lists, dates not examined; 4 boxes
  Consists of various lists used by Booth Tarkington or relevant to the collection.
  - Lists, dates not examined; 4 boxes (Box 252, Box 253, Box 254, Box 255)
- Series 9: Papers of Other Persons, dates not examined; 15 boxes
  Consists of papers of persons other than Booth Tarkington, primarily from family members, but also includes Mrs. Williams Trotter and Brandt and Brandt.
  Arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Brandt and Brandt, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 256)
  - Bu - Lon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 257)
  - Lor - Ro, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 258)
  - Ru - Tarkington, John S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 259)
  - Tarkington, John S. - Tarkington, Louise, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 260)
  - Tarkington, Susanah, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 261)
  - Tarkington Family - Trotter, Elizabeth Stanley, dates not examined; 7 boxes (Box 262, Box 263, Box 264, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267, Box 268)
  - Trotter, Mrs. Williams H. - Ty, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 269)
  - W - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 270)
- Series 10: Oversize Material, 1893-1947; 9 boxes (Box 271, Box 272, Box 273, Box 274, Box 275, Box 276, Box 277, Box 278, Box 279)
  Consists of miscellaneous oversize material, including drawings, photographs, awards, posters, and printed material by and about Booth Tarkington.